Don't lay a finger on those dice,
Josuke Higashikata!
Stay absolutely still.
What's he gonna do now?
If he finds out I've been cheating…
Knowing him,
a simple apology won't be enough.
So what are you looking for?
It could be my imagination,
but I could swear the dice
are staring at me.
Gulp.
Ba-dum, ba-dum…
Hmph. Well, in any case.
Let's continue the game.
ROHAN… ADDS 30 CHIPS
W-Well, you're braver than me…
Just two here.
Catch my drift now, Mr. Alien?
By hook or by crook, I gotta win.
I have to come out
just a little bit ahead.
All right, go!
This guy just doesn't get it!
Guess that's what you call
a streak of luck.
Rolling that score more than once
is certainly possible.
An omen is worth five times
the initial bet, yes?
You'll get your cash.
The dice will do what they do.
Right… I guess strokes of luck
do happen, as they say.
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
EPISODE 28
HIGHWAY GO GO, PART 1
W-W-Wha…
What the hell are you doing?!
I don't know how,
but you are cheating.
It's unacceptable…
It's unacceptable
that I cannot figure it out!
You're freakin' insane!
You're insufferable.
I've been diligent
in restraining myself,
for Mr. Joestar and Koichi's sakes,
but now you've gone
and made it personal.
You're probably gloating inside,
and it makes me sick.
Give me your hand.
I'll have Shining Diamond fix it.
Silence now!
Do you have any idea
why I did that to my little finger?
So you can't back out of the game,
Josuke Higashikata!
I refuse to let a chowderhead like
you disrespect the great Rohan!
We play one more time each.
In that time, I will see through
your method of deception.
Of course, if I cannot
see through your deception…
Before you is two million yen.
Consider it monetary incentive
for treatment by Shining Diamond.
However, if I do uncover
the nature of your deception,
Your little finger is mine,
Josuke Higashikata.
Hey, you two seem to be
enjoying yourselves.
Hey, it's me.
Long time no see, Josuke!
I was stuck in the hospital
for a month.
It's all kinda fuzzy,
supposedly I slammed my
head against the side of the road.
Tamami?
What are you
poking around here for?
I gave him a call and
hired him as a repo man of sorts.
Repo man?
Tamami Kobayashi at your service.
I promise you I will exact
the agreed upon items
swiftly and without fail,
with my trusty soul-affixing lock.
I will fulfill my duty,
regardless of the victor.
My fee is 20%, or 400,000 yen,
whichever is larger.
You both play once more,
and Rohan here tries to determine
the method of deception, yes?
Yes.
What?!
Then again, you could
be tempted to withhold your trick,
so I will make sure
you cannot act on that urge.
Should you win without cheating,
Tamami's lock will
automatically besiege you.
Now I'm really up shit creek…
It's now or never!
I've gotta pull off this trick,
and get myself outta this mess!
So it's settled… I'll go first.
How's that?!
A four!
A pair of three's and a four!
Thank god!
Finally, a normal result for once.
He won't figure it out now.
So it's my turn next, right guys?
Hmph. You look as though a weight's
been lifted off your shoulders.
Like a task you requested
of someone was a success.
Just stay calm.
That bastard Rohan
doesn't have a clue.
I'm gonna do this!
Is that barf?!
Shit! He's getting dizzy!
It's from all of Rohan's shaking.
Josuke! Take your hand
away from the dice.
Huh?
I can't see them.
Shake the dice with your palm open.
Huh? Must be a fire somewhere.
W-What? Sirens?!
Th-This freak's allergic
to the sound of sirens.
Crap! He's gonna revert back!
What are you doing?
You're acting strange!
Show me what you're hiding
in that hand now!
That, my friends,
was a spontaneous battle cry!
Now get ready to be blown away!
Go! Do it!
It's a 666 omen!
The lock didn't activate.
Josuke is cheating!
Well? Did you figure it out,
Rohan-sensei?
Is this an admission of defeat,
Looks like those weird
little dots aren't on Rohan's side.
Just a little longer!
Did you figure it out or not?
Shit, shit, shit…
That's… I've got it!
I'm through!
I've got it! The fire's here!
Huh?!
Rohan-sensei, your house is
burning to the ground!
It was the magnifying glass!
The magnifying glass
started the fire!
We were too distracted by the game!
Shut up! I don't care
if it ends up a heap of ash!
The important thing is that I
figure out how Josuke is cheating!
That's freak in crazy talk!
Escape now,
and take your two million!
W-Well, I'll be going now…
Wait, Josuke!
But first,
I'm gonna fix that finger.
Who asked you to do that…
Josuke, wait! You bastard!
That was close…
I guess I'm the kind of guy that
some people just love to hate, huh?
Who knew…
You seem rather down.
Was I of assistance?
Just be quiet, jeez!
ROHAN KISHIBE'S HOUSE: HALF BURNED
7,000,000 YEN IN FIRE DAMAGE
JOSUKE MAY HAVE ESCAPED UNSCATHED,
BUT HE MANAGED TO GET
EVEN FURTHER ON ROHAN'S BAD SIDE.
Rohan Kishibe's house: half burned
7, 000, 000 yen in fire damage.
Josuke may have escaped unscathed,
but he managed to get
even further on Rohan's bad side.
KAWAJIRI KOSAKU
SHINOBU
HAYATO
Just a reminder to
all you drivers out there
to be extra careful on the road
Seems a motorcycle crashed
at the entrance of
Futatsumori Tunnel yesterday,
and the young rider was badly injured.
Police later found out…
Recently, Mom's been different.
Dressing up, new lipstick,
She's happy…
Did something happen?
It's been a while since Mom
got naked in front of Dad.
Am I the product of parents
who love each other?
What's he doing?
Josuke Higashikata… Jotaro Kujo…
They're the reason I'm in this mess.
Oh, Josuke.
My thanks for yesterday.
So what'd you end up doing
for sleeping and eating yesterday?
Mikitaka! Mikitaka!
Now I want you to stay by my side!
We just moved here, and there are
lots of errands to do.
All right, Mother.
I'll be right there.
H-Huh?
Don't tell me you're telling people
you're an alien again…
You're playing pranks
on people again, aren't you…
I'm sorry if he bothered you.
Pay no attention to him.
At his last school in Tokyo,
people actually took him seriously,
He caused such a scene.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
Huh? What?!
I brainwashed her into
thinking that I'm her son.
"Mikitaka Hazekura"
is my alias here on Earth.
See ya!
Mikitaka! Get over here now!
MIKITAKA HAZEKURA…
ALIEN OR STAND USER?!
H-Huh?
Huh?!
What was that?
Just who was that oddball brat?
Is he truly an alien?
Or is he a Stand user I created
when I threw the arrow at him
and cut his neck?
The way he was able to
drive a wedge
between Josuke and Rohan
was impressive…
But!
Next time it will be the Stand,
Highway Go Go…
It will crush the slime trying to
hunt down my son!
Why can't you look at me?
You could at least say hello.
You know, I am older than you,
Josuke Higashikata.
Sorry about yesterday.
That fire sure was something else.
Yes. Just like in
the movie Pretty Woman,
I lost about 2,500,000 yen
worth of furniture.
Not that any of that bothers me.
So what's wrong? Take a seat.
I swear I will repay you
for yesterday's game.
What?
That was…
Josuke, did you see that?
There was a door to a house
in the tunnel wall.
Someone's inside!
There's a window, too!
Beyond these tunnel walls
is a room.
And someone is living in it!
There's a man, too!
But I can't see their faces!
What is he doing?!
Josuke, did you see that?!
Just shut your face, Rohan Kishibe!
Don't think you can go on
screwing with me forever!
Can no one else see it?
Is that house… a new Stand user?
The man who cut off that woman's hand…
Could he be…
Yoshikage Kira?!
MORIOH LANDMARK 8
"FUTATSUMORI TUNNEL"
COMPLETED IN THE YEAR KAEI 5 (1852),
AND RESTORED IN SHOWA 28,
THE TUNNEL STRETCHES SOME
450 METERS LONG AND
CONNECTS S CITY WITH MORIOH.
ITS CURVED LAYOUT OBSCURES
THE EXIT FROM THE ENTRANCE,
AND ITS LACK OF LIGHT HAS BEEN
THE CAUSE OF NUMEROUS ACCIDENTS.
MOST OF THE AREA'S YOUNGER
POPULATION THINK IT'S HAUNTED.
FUTATSUMORI
TUNNEL
You're telling me a room
was inside the tunnel?!
You're not fooling me!
Is that half-baked lie
your way of getting back at me?
So you have no faith in what
I'm saying, Josuke Higashikata?
Says the liar who cheats with dice…
Says the liar who says one thing
and does another…
You dare have the gall
to accuse me of being a liar?
You and I are
completely different people.
You wouldn't understand
even if I took you back there
to see it myself.
All right, let's go.
That's the exit.
Nothing at all.
Nothing but a wall.
So it was just an illusion.
What?!
CRASH
Th-This is…
This is the room
I saw from the bus.
It appeared out of thin air!
But the man and woman are gone.
Blast it! Something's there!
So this room is a trap!
It's getting closer…
Something's definitely here!
I don't see a thing,
but something's heading toward me!
Something came close.
It was invisible,
but I know it moved toward me.
Something nonhuman.
That room was bait.
That Kira-looking fellow
was an illusion.
There's no question
that room is a Stand.
Going it alone is risky.
I should tell Mr. Joestar…
Shit. It's coming after me!
What is that?!
These… These look like footprints…
They're the Stand?
60km/h!
I lost it.
So it can't run faster than 60km/h.
Long-range Stand…
What?!
Damn! It caught up to me!
I lowered my speed by a fraction!
Bastard…
I'll turn it into a book
and take control!
Heaven's Door!
No… It's sapping my strength…
I was hoping
I'd never see Rohan again,
but here I am.
Guess this liar who never follows
through has a heart after all.
What?!
W-Wait… C-Could this be…
Rohan's motorcycle?
Only his motorcycle?!
SMASH
This monster…
Give me nourishment…
Become my nourishment!
Heaven's Door!
The Stand's name is Highway Go Go.
That room was a trap.
It hunts down anyone
curious enough to enter that room,
then pursues them like a rabid dog,
before relentlessly draining
its victim of all its nutrients.
Once Highway Go Go touches you,
its weakness…
Its weakness…
d-disappears?!
I-It's no use…
I've lost my strength.
I can't even read.
He's depleting more and more
of my strength…
Writing in a command is impossible…
I can't…
Rohan!
Hey, are you here, Rohan?!
Josuke… you actually came back…
So you have a friend…
Your name is Rohan?
Hey, Rohan! Answer me!
Where are you?
Rohan!
Th-That's…
R-Rohan?!
Go ahead, Rohan…
Call out to your friend
to save you.
- What the hell is this?
- Shout out for help.
You okay?!
I've left just a fraction of
your body's nutrients behind.
If you agree to cry to him
for help, I'll spare you your life.
I'll simply deplete him
of his nutrients instead.
Now… Make this easy
and lure him into the room.
I'll let you live.
Hurry and get him in here.
What the hell is this place?
It looks like
someone's living here!
Come on and spit it out.
Look! He's having second thoughts,
he's gonna end up leaving.
It's not like you two actually
care about each other, do you?
Now ask him to save you.
Do you want to die?
I-If I bait him into coming here…
If I give him to you…
w-will you really…
spare my life?
Of course, I promise.
A little give-and-take.
You get me his nutrients,
I give you your life.
Summon him. Lure him here now!
Close, but no cigar.
What?!
You should know that one of
Kishibe Rohan's favorite things
is saying "no" to
extremely powerful people.
Run, Josuke!
If you enter this room,
you're done for!
You'll be killed!
You bastard!
Do you really think
I'm the kind of person
who always does as he's told?
I'll give this dickwad
a proper beating.
Where is he?
Where's this sneaky bastard hiding?
W—
What do you think you're doing,
Josuke Higashikata?
I just told you he's deadly…
You always do the exact opposite
of what I'm thinking.
That's why I despise you.
That's why you bug
the shit out of me!
He's going to attack you!
He already has hold of your scent!
SMASH
CRUSH
Yes! My feast begins!
Heaven's Door!
YOUR BODY WILL FLY
BACKWARDS AT 70 km/h!
Josuke, Highway Go Go will
follow you anywhere at 60km/h!
Look for the user!
Your only way out of this
is to defeat the user!
You just don't shut up, do you!
Rohan!
Rohan Kishibe…
Wow, so you actually saved me…
I'm speechless… I'm speechless
and pretty damn choked up!
All right, Rohan.
I just have to find
that thing's user, right?
Find him
and beat his soul sucking ass
to kingdom come!
Hang in there, Rohan!
EPISODE 29
HIGHWAY GO GO, PART 2